ILGWU Southeast Region Records 5780/058
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Puritan Fashions Corporation. Negotiations., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation. Chatham Dress Corporation., 1965-1969 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation. Chatham Dress Corporation., 1965-1969 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation. Chatham Dress Corporation. Negotiations., 1966-1969 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation. Chatham Dress Corporation. Negotiations., 1966-1969 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation. Hampton Apparel Company., 1966-1969 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation. Hampton Apparel Company., 1966-1969 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation. Hampton Apparel Company. Agreement., 1961-1963 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation. Walterboro Dress Corporation., 1965-1969 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation. Waterboro Dress Corporation., 1957-1964 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- "R" Correspondence. Misc., 1957-1968 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- "R" Correspondence. Misc., 1950-1954 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Ray-Shire Dress Manufacturing Company., 1949-1953 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Ray Lee, Inc., 1958 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- "R" Correspondence. Misc., 1949-1953 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Research Department., 1946-1951 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Research Department., 1951-1955 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Rhea Manufacturing Company. [folder 1 of 2], 1954-1955 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Rhea Manufacturing Company. [folder 2 of 2], 1954-1955 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Rhea Manufacturing Company., 1955-1956 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Rhea Manufacturing Company., 1959-1960 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Rita Dress Company., 1955 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- "S" Correspondence. Misc., 1950-1959 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- "S" Correspondence. Misc., 1959-1960 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- "S" Correspondence. Misc., 1960-1969 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Sands Manufacturing Company., 1966-1967 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  Case No. 11-RC-2498
- Sands Manufacturing Company. Statements., 1966-1967 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- "S" Correspondence. Misc., 1957-1960 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Southern States. Misc., 1967 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Schooltimer, Inc., 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Segalock Fasteners, Inc., 1949-1950 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Serbin, Inc., 1956 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Southeastern Region., 1955-1962 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Southeast Shop Stewards' School., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Southeastern Regional Office. New Shops., 1949-1955 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Southeastern Regional Office. New Shops., 1955 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Signal Knitting Mills, Inc., 1944-1951 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Signal Knitting Mills, Inc., 1952-1955 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Signal Knitting Mills, Inc., 1955-1960 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Signal Knitting Mills, Inc., 1956 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Signal Knitting Mills, Inc., 1955-1957 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Signal Knitting Mills, Inc., 1957-1958 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Signal Knitting Mills, Inc., 1960-1962 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Signal Knitting Mills, Inc., 1962-1967 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Signal Knitting Mills, Inc. Negotiations., 1964-1965 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Signal Knitting Mills, Inc., 1964-1970 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Signal Knitting Mills, Inc. Carden "CB" Charge., 1966-1969 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Signal Knitting Mills, Inc. and Dri-Set Corporation. Agreement., 1967-1969 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Southeastern Regional Office., 1953 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Southeastern Regional Office. [folder 1 of 2], 1954-1955 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Southeastern Regional Office. [folder 2 of 2], 1954-1955 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Southeastern Regional Office., 1957-1958 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Southeastern Regional Office., 1960 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Southeastern Regional Office. Conference., 1960 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Southeastern Regional Conferences., 1965-1967 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Southeastern Regional Conferences., 1969 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Southern Garment Company, Inc., 1958 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- "Southern Garment Worker". Misc., 1966 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Southern Maid Garment Company, Inc., 1947-1954 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Southern Maid Garment Company, Inc., 1954-1957 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Southern Regional Council., 1957-1967 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Spartan Undies, Inc., 1956 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Spartan Undies, Inc. Negotiations., 1966-1968 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Spartan Undies, Inc. Agreement., 1964-1967 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Spartan Undies, Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Sportee Corporation of North Carolina., 1969 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Standard Knitting Mills, Inc., 1954-1961 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Standard Workers and Organizing Committee., 1956 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Standard Workers and Organizing Committee., 1956-1957 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Standard Textile Mills, Inc., 1958 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Standard Textile Mills, Inc., 1960-1962 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Southeastern Regional Office., 1945-1954 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Strutwear, Inc., 1953 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Stulberg, Louis. Correspondence., 1968-1969 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Stulberg, Louis. Correspondence., 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Stulberg, Louis. Correspondence., 1962-1967 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Stulberg, Louis. Correspondence., 1958-1961 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Stulberg, Louis. Correspondence., 1957-1958 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Stulberg, Louis. Correspondence., 1950-1957 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Sunshine Fashions, Inc., 1963-1965 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Sunshine Fashions, Inc., 1963-1966 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Sunshine Fashions, Inc., 1966 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- "T" Correspondence. Misc., 1957-1959 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Talon, Inc., 1959-1962 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Talon, Inc., 1957-1959 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Tennessee State Labor Council., 1958-1960 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Tex-Son, Inc., 1959 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Textile Workers Organizing Committee., 1937-1958 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Textile Workers of America., 1937-1958 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Thompson Sub-Committee., 1966-1967 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Thorsby Garment Company, Inc., 1960-1965 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Thorsby Garment Company, Inc., 1957-1960 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Thrift Dye Works., 1960 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Toccoa Garment Company, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Toccoa Garment Company, Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Training Institute, ILGWU., 1958-1960 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Tyler, Gus. Correspondence., 1960-1971 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Umhey, F.F. Correspondence., 1950-1954 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Union Label Department., 1958-1960 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Union Label Department., 1961-1962 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Union Label Department., 1965-1969 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Union Label Department. Marguerite Hill., 1967-1969 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- United Mills, Inc., 1949-1953 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Unity Broadcasting Corporation., 1945-1948 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Unity Broadcasting Corporation., 1948-1949 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Upper South Department., 1946-1962 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- "V" Correspondence. Misc., 1960-1967 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Vacation Time., 1954 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- "W" Correspondence. Misc., 1957-1961 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Wage Stabilization Board., 1951 (Box 76, Folder 12)
- Walterboro Manufacturing Company., 1953 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Walterboro Manufacturing Company., 1953-1954 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Walterboro Manufacturing Company., 1955-1957 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Walterboro Dress Corporation., 1958-1964 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- War Relief Fund., 1944-1946 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Wentworth Manufacturing Company., 1951-1953 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Wentworth Manufacturing Company., 1953-1955 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Wentworth Manufacturing Company., 1954-1956 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Wentworth Manufacturing Company., 1957-1958 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Wentworth Manufacturing Company., 1958-1960 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Wentworth Manufacturing Company., 1962-1965 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Wentworth Manufacturing Company., 1965-1966 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Whitehaven Distribution Center, Inc., 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Wind 'N Sky, Inc., 1963-1965 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Workers Education Local 189., 1952-1955 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- X-L, Inc., 1963-1965 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- "Y" and "Z" Correspondence. Misc., 1957-1959 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Zimmerman, Charles. Correspondence., 1958-1961 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Weekly Reports. James Reufroe., 1959 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. Mason Landon., 1959 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Walter Ashley., 1959 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Jerome Levine., 1959 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Russel McMahan., 1959 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. J.R. Light., 1959 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. William Krost., 1959 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. Eddie. D. Lee., 1959 (Box 79, Folder 8)
- Weekly Reports. Russel McMahan., 1959 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. WM Von Bach., 1959 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Eugene W. Sutherland., 1959 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Samuel Wharton, Jr., 1959 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. J.C. Willis., 1959 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. Harry Metz., 1959 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Lena Young., 1959 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. James Reufroe., 1960 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. Waymon Mitchell., 1960 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. J.W. Mitchell., 1960 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Robert Oliver., 1960 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Edwin Sharp., 1960 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. Ruby Chaney., 1972 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. Bill Andrews., 1972 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Carl Stafford., 1972 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Edwin Sharp., 1972 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Frances Munroe., 1972 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. Dorothy Mims., 1972 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Erma Mackey., 1972 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. Robert Dehil., 1972 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Weekly Reports. W.B. Chisholm., 1972 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Weekly Reports. Rebecca Heyfurth., 1972 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Weekly Reports. Willie Presley., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. Burl C. Robinson., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Imogene Ross., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. [Illegible]., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Jerry (?)., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. Claudette Taylor., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Ethel Vick., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. Inez Kelley., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Weekly Reports. Peggy Hall., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Weekly Reports. Pauline Jordan., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Weekly Reports. Christine Smith., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Weekly Reports. Huston Parker., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Weekly Reports. Velva White., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 13)
- Weekly Reports. Pauline Jordan., 1972 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. Spurgeon Griggs., 1972 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Thomas Boone., 1972 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Claudette Taylor., 1972 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Bill Andrews., 1972 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. [Illegible]., 1972 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Burl C. Robinson., 1972 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. Jerry McDaniel., 1972 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Weekly Reports. Dorothy Branham., 1972 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Weekly Reports. Lillian Kolwyck., 1972 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- Weekly Reports. Benny D., 1972 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Weekly Reports. Russel McMahan., 1972 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. Rebecca Hall., 1972 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Spurgeon Griggs., 1972 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Peggy Hall., 1972 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Anthony De Roberts., 1972 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. Inez Kelley., 1972 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Erma Mackey., 1972 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. Lena Young., 1972 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Weekly Reports. Leone Craig., 1972 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- Weekly Reports. Earl F., 1972 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Weekly Reports. Pauline Bennett., 1972 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Weekly Reports. Pauline Jordan., 1972 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- Weekly Reports. Roy Stewart., 1973 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. Jerry McDaniel., 1972 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Spurgeon Griggs., 1973 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Clarence Loftin., 1972-1973 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Robert B(?)., 1973 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. Lillian Kolwyck., 1972 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Mason London., 1972 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. Inez Kelley., 1972 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Weekly Reports. Benny D., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. Erma Mackey., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Bill Andrews., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Anthony De Roberts., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Ethel Vick., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. Inez Kelley., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Robert Dehil., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. Velva White., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Weekly Reports. Lillian Kolwyck., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Weekly Reports. Gwen Catham., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Weekly Reports. Peggy Hall., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Weekly Reports. Bobby Wray., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 12)
- Weekly Reports. Pauline Jordan., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 13)
- Weekly Reports. Mary Cameron., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 14)
- Weekly Reports. Jerry McDaniel., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 15)
- Weekly Reports. Mason London., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 16)
- Weekly Reports. Robert Bert., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 17)
- Weekly Reports. Lena M., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 18)
- Weekly Reports. Perry Burke., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 19)
- Weekly Reports. Frances Caldwell., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 20)
- Weekly Reports. Thomas Boone., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 21)
- Weekly Reports. Bernice Taylor., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 22)
- Weekly Reports. Rebecca Hall., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 23)
- Weekly Reports. Illegible., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 24)
- Weekly Reports. D.O. Warren., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 25)
- Weekly Reports. Spurgeon Griggs., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 26)
- Weekly Reports. Leone Craig., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 27)
- Weekly Reports. Earl F., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 28)
- Weekly Reports. Hutson Parker., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 29)
- Weekly Reports. Peggy Hall., 1973 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. M. Cameron., 1973 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Jenny McDaniel., 1973 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Mason London., 1973 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Robert Bert., 1973 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. D.O. Warren., 1973 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Claudette Taylor., 1973 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. Rebecca Heyfurth., 1973 (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Weekly Reports. Rebecca Hall., 1973 (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Weekly Reports. Dorothy L., 1973 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. Mary Cameron., 1973 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Perry Burke., 1973 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Hutson Parker., 1973 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Willie Presley., 1973 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. Leone Craig., 1973 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Bill Andrews., 1973 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. [Illegible]., 1973 (Box 89, Folder 8)
- Weekly Reports. Claudette Taylor., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. Gwen Chatham., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. W.B. Chisholm. [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. W.B. Chisholm. [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Milford (?)., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. Robert Dehil., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Roy Stewart., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. Clarence Loftin., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Weekly Reports. Carl Stafford., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Weekly Reports. John Curtis., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 10)
- Weekly Reports. Russel McMahan., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 11)
- Weekly Reports. Benny D., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 12)
- Weekly Reports. Edwin Sharp., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 13)
- Weekly Reports. Dorothy Mims., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 14)
- Weekly Reports. J.R. Light., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 15)
- Weekly Reports. Mary Ellen Edgin., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 16)
- Weekly Reports. Willie Presley., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 17)
- Weekly Reports. Pauline Jordan., 1973 (Box 90, Folder 18)
- Weekly Reports. Mason London., 1973 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. Christine Smith., 1973 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Imogene Ross., 1973 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Burl C. Robinson., 1973 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Jenny McDaniel., 1973 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. Peter Little., 1973 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Frances Munroe., 1973 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. Willie Presley., 1973 (Box 91, Folder 8)
- Weekly Reports. Ethel Vick., 1973 (Box 91, Folder 9)
- Weekly Reports. Bill Andrews., 1973 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. Rebecca Hall., 1973 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Leone Craig., 1973 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Benny D., 1973 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Thomas Boone., 1973 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. Lena Young., 1973 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Weekly Report. [Illegible]., 1973 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Weekly Report. Hutson Parker., 1973 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Weekly Report. Russel McMahan., 1973 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Weekly Reports. Dorothy Mims., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. D.O. Warren., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Claudette Taylor., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Bernice Taylor., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Lena Young., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. [Illegible]., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Velva White., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. Ethel Vick., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Weekly Reports. Jerry Tucker., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 9)
- Weekly Reports. W.B. Chisholm., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 10)
- Weekly Reports. Brenda Hoover., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- Weekly Reports. Carl Stafford., 1973 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. Lillian Kolwyck., 1973 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Rebecca Heyfurth., 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Peggy Hall., 1973 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Gwen Catham., 1973 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. Robert Dehil., 1973 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Erma Mackey., 1973 (Box 94, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. Mary Cameron., 1973 (Box 94, Folder 8)
- Weekly Reports. Edwin Sharp., 1973 (Box 94, Folder 9)
- Weekly Reports. Pauline Jordan., 1973 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. Anthony De Roberts., 1973 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Inez Kelley., 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Mary Ellen Edgin., 1973 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Earl Tanner., 1973 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. Brenda Hoover. [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Brenda Hoover. [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. Spurgeon Griggs., 1973 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Weekly Reports. J.R. Light. [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. J.R. Light. [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Thomas Boone., 1973 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Perry Burke., 1973 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Mary Ellen Edgin., 1973 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. Anthony De Roberts., 1973 (Box 96, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Dorothy Ledd., 1973 (Box 96, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. Frances Caldwell., 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Weekly Reports. Burl Robinson., 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Weekly Reports. Earl Tanner., 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Weekly Reports. Bernice Taylor., 1973 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Weekly Reports. Carl Stafford., 1973 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Weekly Reports. Edwin Sharp., 1973 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Weekly Reports. Dorothy Mims., 1973 (Box 97, Folder 7)
- Weekly Reports. Erma Mackey., 1973 (Box 97, Folder 8)
- Southern Garment Workers., 1967-1971 (Box 97, Folder 9)
- Southern Garment Workers., 1976-1988 (Box 97, Folder 10)
- Underwear Union News., 1946 (Box 97, Folder 11)